

NGUYEN ANH TUAN

Head Chef



nanhtuan85@gmail.com

About

With over a decade of experience in the food processing industry, I have honed my skills in both hotel and resort settings in Ho Chi Minh City. My career has been marked by a dedication to excellence in culinary arts and food service management. I am now seeking an executive position where I can leverage my extensive expertise and passion for the culinary arts to achieve my goal of becoming a Head Chef, in a top-tier professional hotel/resort/restaurant environment.



0902696110



District 10, Ho Chi Minh City

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

- Jul 2024, Michelin selected at Mía Dinning
- Mar 2015, Chef Trainer certification
- Dec 2015, Service Excellence certification
- Nov2016, Food hygiene and Safety seminar certification
- Aug2017, N5 Japanese Certification

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Japan Elementary

EDUCATION

- 2006
 Intermediate
 Tourism and hotel of Ho Chi Minh City
 (Saigon Tourist)
- 2005
 Intermediate
 Food Technology College

EXPERIENCE

12/2023 - 07/2024 **Head Chef**Mía Dining **Central prod**

Control production processes and kitchen operation to the restaurant standards.

Prepare a new menu in accordance with the restaurant's business needs.

Plan and organize training for kitchen staff...

08/2022 - 10/2023 Head Chef
Diamond lounge

Plan, prepare and implement high quality food products, and set-ups in all areas in the kitchen. Work seamlessly with recipes, standards and plating guides.

Maintain all hygiency asn

Maintain all hygiency aspects within the

kitchen operation.

Use appropriately all equipment, tools and

machines.

Ensure high levels of cleanliness and low levels of loss and breakages. Control production.

Exercise maximum control on wastage to

achieve optimum profitability.

Ensure that recipes and costings are established

and updated.

03/2021 - 06/2022 Sous Chef

La Casa
Dining and bar

Control kitchen system (menu, cost, hygiene,...)
Work closely with the Head Chef in determining
the quantity of food items and ingredients to be
produced, bought or prepared for that day.
Monitor food quality and quantity to ensure the
most economical usage of ingredients.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Gender: Male

Birthday: 13/08/1985

Marital status: Married

Nationality: Vietnam

CAREER INFORMATION

Level: Manager

Salary: 1.600 - 3.000 USD

Location: Ho Chi Minh City, Lam Dong,

Khanh Hoa

Industry: Education/Training,

Restaurant/Hotel/Resort

EXPERIENCE

Sous Chef 7/2017-03/2021

Sherwood Support Executive Chef: New menu, hygiene, staff,

Suites Hotel stock and store,...

Ensure that team members have a complete

understanding of and adhere to the

hotel's team member rules and regulations.

Work closely with the Chefs, meeting regularly to determine menu selections and specials that is both

satisfying to guest and profitable to the outlet.

Chef de Partie 10/2014 - 03/2017

The Reverie Saigon Food hygiene, creation and fixation a new recipe, Hotel

organization, set up of kitchen, customers complain

handing.

Chef de Partie 10/2012 - 7/2014

The Grand Ho Tram Staff training, menu planning, food function, coffee Strip

break, a la carte service.

Follow and ensure a standard Head chef's menu. Every day, report kitchen activities (by shift) to the

Sous chef.

CULINARY INVENTION



Potatoes and rice chip



Bouillabaisse soup



Tangerine mousse



Salmon Tartare